{"id": "search_qa_0", "question": "I'm tired of Cuisinart and grey pans, got anything else? Give me a product ID for a different brand and color.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Do I require specialized cleaning agents for the pan to maintain its like-new appearance?\nA: no", "answer": "No answer, the provided product information doesn't include an ASIN or product ID, and there is no information about other products.", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_0", "question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU"}
{"id": "search_qa_1", "question": "I'm not messing around with cheap brands. Give me a pan from Copper Chef or Lodge that can handle temperatures above 600F.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY"}
{"id": "fact_qa_1", "question": "Is the stainless steel pan resistant to warping when exposed to high heat?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the ZWILLING Spirit Fry Pan prone to warping?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I use high heat while cooking with stainless steel cookware to avoid damaging the pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU"}
{"id": "fact_qa_2", "question": "Is there a warranty included with the purchase of the T-fal Handy Pot?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the T-fal pot contain any harmful toxins in its materials or non-stick coating?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is a cover included with the Cuisinart FCT23-24NS Crepe Pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Cuisinart saucepan manufactured in the United States?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964"}
{"id": "search_qa_2", "question": "I ain't paying more than 10 dollars and I only want either a black or green one. Give me the pan that matches these specifics.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Stone Earth Pan lighter than traditional cast iron pans?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_3", "question": "What is the depth measurement of the pan?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Are there particular considerations for what I should refrain from cooking in this pan?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this pan designed to be dishwasher-safe?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU"}
{"id": "fact_qa_4", "question": "Is the Cuisinart Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan compatible with induction cooktops?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00008CM69"}
{"id": "fact_qa_5", "question": "Is the Utopia Kitchen Cast Iron Skillet suitable for cooking a steak to medium-rare doneness?", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_6", "question": "Is the non-stick surface of this ceramic-coated pan resistant to damage from acidic foods when used according to the manufacturer's instructions?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the non-stick coating of this pan durable enough to withstand frequent cooking of acidic foods without damage?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is it recommended to cook acidic foods in this pan before a good patina has been established?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Are the non-stick ceramic coated pans dishwasher safe?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y"}
{"id": "fact_qa_7", "question": "Can the T-fal A8572494 saucepan be used for cooking on high heat?", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964"}
{"id": "search_qa_3", "question": "I gotta roast some veggies and need a pan that can stomach a solid 400F in the oven. Oh, and it's gotta be green, don't ask. Got anything like that?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this pan appropriate for roasting a chicken?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_0", "question": "I am in search of eco-friendly cookware. Do these pans align with that objective?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Will this pan allow my food to cook evenly on all types of stoves?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_1", "question": "Is it safe to prepare all kinds of food in this pan without concern for flavor changes?", "answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_2", "question": "Is this pan durable enough to handle frequent use for preparing various cuisines?", "answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B00BK89AYS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_8", "question": "Is the pan suitable for both baking and broiling?", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU"}
{"id": "fact_qa_9", "question": "What is the maximum oven-safe temperature for the Copper Chef pan?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it safe to leave the Copper Chef pan on high heat for an extended period without causing damage?\nA: no", "answer": "850", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM"}
{"id": "search_qa_4", "question": "I got a soft spot for ZWILLING J.A. Henckels and Norpro, but I can't drop more than 30 dollars. What's the cheapest pan you have from either of those brands?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set suitable for cooking methods other than broiling?\nA: yes", "answer": "18.55", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_3", "question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_10", "question": "Is there a manufacturer warranty included with these pans?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Are these pans dishwasher safe?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set manufactured using authentic stainless steel?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE"}
{"id": "search_qa_5", "question": "I ain't paying more than 10 bucks for a pan, and it sure as hell ain't gonna be from Copper Chef. So, what's the largest pan you can offer for that price?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is a 10-inch pan appropriate for cooking meals for a single individual?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the 12-inch pan designed to accommodate the cooking needs of singles and smaller families?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_4", "question": "Is this pan suitable for acidic sauces, given that it's not dishwasher safe?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it advisable to frequently cook acidic foods such as tomato sauce in this pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this saucepan dishwasher-safe?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the saucepan dishwasher safe according to the manufacturer's recommendations?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B002UNMZPS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_11", "question": "Is the Anolon saucepan suitable for making candy that requires precise temperature control?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the T-fal A8572494 saucepan be used for cooking on high heat?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the saucepan suitable for preparing delicate sauces and reductions?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this saucepan oven-safe?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK"}
{"id": "fact_qa_12", "question": "What is the material composition of the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set?", "answer": "stainless steel", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU"}
{"id": "fact_qa_13", "question": "What type of warranty is included with the purchase of these pans?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Are these pans dishwasher safe?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0170TFNXM"}
{"id": "search_qa_6", "question": "I'm all about the big guns when it comes to pans and I dig Anolon and Ozeri brands. Hook me up with the largest one they got that's over 10 inches.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is a 10-inch pan appropriate for cooking meals for a single individual?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes", "answer": "There is no matching product", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM"}
{"id": "search_qa_7", "question": "I'm in the market for a large pan, needs to be blue or silver, anything over 12 inches will do. But it's got to handle some heat, what's the highest oven-safe temperature pan you got in those colors?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "450", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY"}
{"id": "search_qa_8", "question": "I'm looking for a big pan, preferable in grey or black color, but I don't want it if it's from Tramontina. What's the biggest one you got that matches what I'm looking for?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan designed for Madeleines suitable for baking other similar-sized desserts?\nA: yes", "answer": "ASIN: B000000000", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0170TFNXM"}
{"id": "fact_qa_14", "question": "Does the pan's actual weight correspond to the listed weight of 2.6 pounds in the description?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Stone Earth Pan lighter than traditional cast iron pans?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pot considered lightweight by customers?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the 12-inch pan designed to accommodate the cooking needs of singles and smaller families?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_5", "question": "I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?", "answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_6", "question": "Is this pan designed to be presentable on a table setting?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is this pan designed to be presentable for table service?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: My cupboard space is quite limited; is this pan designed for convenient storage when it's not in use?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this pan designed to be dishwasher-safe?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B00008CM69"}
{"id": "fact_qa_15", "question": "Do users report any balance or weight distribution problems when handling these pans?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: If I don't conscientiously maintain this pan, will its appearance alter as time goes by?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Does baking bread goods in a heavy pan affect the evenness of heat distribution?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0170TFNXM"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_7", "question": "Is it possible to utilize this pan for cooking on the stovetop as well as presenting food at the dining table?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Will this pan allow my food to cook evenly on all types of stoves?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this pan designed to be presentable for table service?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964"}
{"id": "fact_qa_16", "question": "Does the pan become non-stick after proper seasoning and use over time?", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY"}
{"id": "fact_qa_17", "question": "Does the frying pan become non-stick following seasoning?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the pan become non-stick after proper seasoning and use over time?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is prior seasoning required for this non-stick ceramic coated pan before its initial use?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?\nA: no", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY"}
{"id": "fact_qa_18", "question": "Is the Tramontina pan compatible with gas cooktops and does it provide even heat distribution when used on them?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is this pan compatible with various stove types?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0"}
{"id": "fact_qa_19", "question": "What material is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of?", "answer": "stainless steel", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU"}
{"id": "fact_qa_20", "question": "Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B002UNMZPS"}
{"id": "search_qa_9", "question": "I'm a big fan of Lodge, what's the cheapest pan they have in your store?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Stone Earth Pan lighter than traditional cast iron pans?\nA: yes", "answer": "No", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE"}
{"id": "search_qa_10", "question": "I'm looking to add a pop of color to my kitchen. Do you have any blue pans in your product line?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Do I need to purchase any extra cleaning supplies when I buy this pan?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_8", "question": "Can this pan withstand frequent washing if I regularly run my kitchenware through the dishwasher?", "answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_9", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with this pan, or is it better to refrain from doing so?", "answer": "No", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM"}
{"id": "fact_qa_21", "question": "Can the tempered-glass lid be used with different sizes and brands of cookware?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is this pan compatible with various stove types?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this fry pan compatible with an electric glass top stove?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Will this pan allow my food to cook evenly on all types of stoves?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY"}
{"id": "fact_qa_22", "question": "Can the heavy-gauge, hard-anodized aluminum saucepan be used on a glass top range?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the T-fal A8572494 saucepan be used for cooking on high heat?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the saucepan suitable for high-temperature cooking on the stovetop without damaging its nonstick coating?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it safe to use metal utensils with this non-stick saucepan?\nA: no", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK"}
{"id": "fact_qa_23", "question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00134LXEY"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_10", "question": "Is it acceptable to clean this pan using only soap and water, or does it have specific cleaning instructions?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I follow any specific precautions when cleaning this pan to preserve its surface?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I follow any particular precautions when cleaning this pan to preserve its surface?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the frying pan be safely cleaned in a dishwasher?\nA: no", "answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY"}
{"id": "fact_qa_24", "question": "Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00008CM69"}
{"id": "search_qa_11", "question": "I'm a bit of a home chef, and I need a pan that can withstand the heat. What's the top pan you have from either Presto or Tramontina that can handle over 400F in the oven?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_11", "question": "I'm in search of sustainable cookware options. Would purchasing these pans align with that objective?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B00134LXEY"}
{"id": "search_qa_12", "question": "I do a lot of high-heat cooking, so I need a pan that can handle at least 400F and is larger than the average size. What's the best option you got?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B002UNMZPS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_25", "question": "Can using cooking spray damage non-stick cookware surfaces?", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_26", "question": "Does the pan's exterior offer the same durability and ease of cleaning as the interior?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00BK89AYS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_27", "question": "Is the T-fal pan compatible with induction cooktops?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_12", "question": "Can this pan be safely used for recipes that call for broiling?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for both baking and broiling?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set suitable for cooking methods other than broiling?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this pan durable enough to handle frequent use for preparing various cuisines?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B00008CM69"}
{"id": "search_qa_13", "question": "I need a new pan, but I'm a loyal Presto fan and my wallet can't handle anything north of 20 dollars. You got anything that ain't gonna break the bank?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00134LXEY"}
{"id": "search_qa_14", "question": "Listen, I've had enough of Norpro. Get me the most affordable pan from another brand that can handle at least 450 degrees in the oven.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set suitable for cooking methods other than broiling?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes", "answer": "ASIN not found in the provided product information.", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM"}
{"id": "fact_qa_28", "question": "Is the pan suitable for baking submarine sandwich loaves?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for both baking and broiling?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the USA Pan Hearth Bread Pan appropriate for baking gluten-free bread?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B002UNMZPS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_29", "question": "Can the Stone Earth Frying Pan's non-stick coating withstand the use of acidic ingredients such as tomato sauce without damage?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the non-stick coating of this pan durable enough to withstand frequent cooking of acidic foods without damage?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is it advisable to frequently cook acidic foods such as tomato sauce in this pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it recommended to cook acidic foods in this pan before a good patina has been established?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00BK89AYS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_30", "question": "What is the duration and type of warranty provided with the USA Pan Hearth Bread Pan?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the USA Pan Hearth Bread Pan appropriate for baking gluten-free bread?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this pan designed to withstand repeated use for batch baking?\nA: yes", "answer": "Not specified", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B002UNMZPS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_31", "question": "Is this T-fal pan dishwasher safe?", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78"}
{"id": "fact_qa_32", "question": "What type of protection is included with the pans for storage?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: What material is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of?\nA: stainless steel\nExample 3:\nQ: Are there particular considerations for what I should refrain from cooking in this pan?\nA: yes", "answer": "No information is provided in the product information about protection for storage, however, the information does mention a \"3-piece set\", which may imply that the pans are designed to be stacked together for storage purposes.", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE"}
{"id": "search_qa_15", "question": "I'm looking for a pan that's bigger than 8 inches, doesn't cost more than 20 dollars, and can handle some heat in the oven. Give me your best option.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is a 10-inch pan appropriate for cooking meals for a single individual?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the 12-inch pan designed to accommodate the cooking needs of singles and smaller families?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964"}
{"id": "search_qa_16", "question": "I'm trying to save some money and can’t afford anything over 10 dollars. What's the cheapest pan you have?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is a 10-inch pan appropriate for cooking meals for a single individual?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_33", "question": "Does the non-stick coating on this pan maintain its durability over time with proper use?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the pan become non-stick after proper seasoning and use over time?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: If I don't maintain this pan consistently, will its appearance alter over time?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_34", "question": "Are use and care instructions included with the purchase of this cast iron skillet for first-time users?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet come already seasoned?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is seasoning the pan necessary before using it for the first time?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is prior seasoning required for this non-stick ceramic coated pan before its initial use?\nA: no", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_35", "question": "Are replacement parts available for purchase for the Presto 5900 Electric Wok, like new legs or a glass lid?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the Presto 5900 wok be recommended for professional or commercial kitchen environments?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this fry pan compatible with an electric glass top stove?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY"}
{"id": "search_qa_17", "question": "I ain't too impressed with Ozeri, so show me some other brand's pan that's at least 10 inches. And no funny business, show me the first one you find.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is a 10-inch pan appropriate for cooking meals for a single individual?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no", "answer": "ASIN:B00005OUOC", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00BK89AYS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_36", "question": "Is this pan compatible with induction cooktops?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_13", "question": "If I don't maintain this pan consistently, will its appearance alter over time?", "answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_37", "question": "Is the red Thermo-Spot on the cookware designed to maintain its color over time with regular use?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Does the pan become non-stick after proper seasoning and use over time?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: If I don't maintain this pan consistently, will its appearance alter over time?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78"}
{"id": "fact_qa_38", "question": "Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_14", "question": "Is this pan ready for immediate use on an induction cooktop straight from the packaging?", "answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY"}
{"id": "search_qa_18", "question": "Look, I'm not shelling out more than 30 dollars for a pan but it's gotta be larger than 12 inches. What's the best option you got for me?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the 12-inch pan designed to accommodate the cooking needs of singles and smaller families?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is a 10-inch pan appropriate for cooking meals for a single individual?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0170TFNXM"}
{"id": "fact_qa_39", "question": "How does the weight of these die-cast aluminum pans compare to cast iron pans for handling?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Stone Earth Pan lighter than traditional cast iron pans?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Does using cast iron cookware provide health benefits over nonstick pans due to its lack of synthetic coatings and iron contribution to food?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: What is the material composition of the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set?\nA: stainless steel", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_40", "question": "Are the pans in the Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri compatible with induction cooktops?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE"}
{"id": "search_qa_19", "question": "I'm trying to match my kitchen decor and I want a big, blue pan. What's the cheapest one you got that's 12 inches or bigger?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the 12-inch pan designed to accommodate the cooking needs of singles and smaller families?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00008CM69"}
{"id": "fact_qa_41", "question": "Does the product's nonstick coating contain PFOA?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0"}
{"id": "fact_qa_42", "question": "Are customers generally satisfied with the non-stick quality of this product?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Does the pan become non-stick after proper seasoning and use over time?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y"}
{"id": "fact_qa_43", "question": "Is this product compatible with induction cooktops as well as other types of cooktops?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y"}
{"id": "fact_qa_44", "question": "Does the interior of the pot include measurement marks?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964"}
{"id": "search_qa_20", "question": "I don't want any black pan, and it needs to handle at least 450F. What's the cheapest option does your store offer?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Should oven temperature be reduced to avoid over-browning when using dark non-stick pans for baking?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM"}
{"id": "fact_qa_45", "question": "Is the ZWILLING Spirit Fry Pan prone to warping?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y"}
{"id": "search_qa_21", "question": "Look, I gotta avoid grey, but I'm keen on either Presto or Bialetti brands for pans. Which can tolerate the highest oven heat from these specific brands?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Should oven temperature be reduced to avoid over-browning when using dark non-stick pans for baking?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_46", "question": "Is the pan lighter or heavier compared to similar cookware products?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Stone Earth Pan lighter than traditional cast iron pans?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pot considered lightweight by customers?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78"}
{"id": "fact_qa_47", "question": "Does the non-stick surface of the pan maintain its performance over time with proper care?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Does the pan become non-stick after proper seasoning and use over time?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: If I don't maintain this pan consistently, will its appearance alter over time?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_15", "question": "Should I follow any specific precautions when cleaning this pan to preserve its surface?", "answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B00134LXEY"}
{"id": "fact_qa_48", "question": "Does the pan's ergonomic handle successfully ease the handling of the pan's weight?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the lid of this pan designed to be easily handled by someone with arthritis?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Might the pan's shape render it difficult to stow in a drawer alongside other kitchen tools?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM"}
{"id": "fact_qa_49", "question": "Is the Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet compatible with induction cooktops?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?\nA: no", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_50", "question": "Is this saucepan oven-safe?", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00008CM69"}
{"id": "fact_qa_51", "question": "Are the silicone-coated handles of cookware resistant to high temperatures?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the GREBLON ceramic coating on cookware safe from releasing toxic chemicals when used at high temperatures?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Should I use high heat while cooking with stainless steel cookware to avoid damaging the pan?\nA: no", "answer": "There is no information about silicone-coated handles in the product details.", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_52", "question": "Can the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan be safely placed in an oven?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan be used on induction cooktops or in the oven?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this saucepan oven-safe?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE"}
{"id": "search_qa_22", "question": "I don't have a lot of dough to spend, but I need a Utopia Kitchen pan that won't cost more than 30 dollars and can handle high oven temperatures. What's the best one you've got?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY"}
{"id": "search_qa_23", "question": "I don't want a Tramontina, show me the cheapest alternative you have in your pan range.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "answer": "ASIN is not available in the provided product information. However, I can tell you that the product shown is not Tramontina, it's Anolon, and its price is $55.99.", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK"}
{"id": "search_qa_24", "question": "I'm hunting for a black pan. Preferably All-Clad or USA Pan. Which one of those can withstand the highest oven temperature?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "No", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY"}
{"id": "fact_qa_53", "question": "Do the pot's handles provide comfort and safety when handling?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Do the riveted handles on kitchenware create challenges when cleaning around them?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pot considered lightweight by customers?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the lid of this pan designed to be easily handled by someone with arthritis?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964"}
{"id": "fact_qa_54", "question": "Is this pan designed to withstand repeated use for batch baking?", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00134LXEY"}
{"id": "search_qa_25", "question": "I'm not messing around anymore with pans that warp under high heat. Which one of your pans can handle temperatures of over 500 degrees Fahrenheit? Give me the first one you get.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0"}
{"id": "fact_qa_55", "question": "Does cooking with this wok provide energy savings compared to using a traditional stove?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does this wok provide an effective traditional stir-fry cooking experience?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is sticking a common issue with this wok when cooking food?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the Presto 5900 wok be recommended for professional or commercial kitchen environments?\nA: no", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY"}
{"id": "fact_qa_56", "question": "Is this pan designed to be dishwasher-safe?", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0"}
{"id": "fact_qa_57", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with this cast iron skillet without scratching it?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it safe to use metal utensils with this nonstick pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is it safe to use metal utensils with the non-stick surface of this pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it safe to use metal utensils with this pan, or is it better to refrain from doing so?\nA: no", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_16", "question": "I frequently encounter issues with pans failing to heat uniformly on my stove. Does this design assist in promoting even heat distribution?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Will this pan allow my food to cook evenly on all types of stoves?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE"}
{"id": "search_qa_26", "question": "I've got a thing against All-Clad and I'm dead set on grey. Show me the first pan that you've got that fits that description.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: What is the material composition of the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set?\nA: stainless steel\nExample 2:\nQ: If I don't conscientiously maintain this pan, will its appearance alter as time goes by?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Stone Earth Pan lighter than traditional cast iron pans?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00BK89AYS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_58", "question": "Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00BK89AYS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_59", "question": "Is a metal spatula suitable for use with this non-stick pan?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_60", "question": "Is it necessary to season the All-Clad Stainless 10-inch fry pan in the same way as a cast iron pan?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_61", "question": "What is the weight characteristic of this pan as reported by users?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Stone Earth Pan lighter than traditional cast iron pans?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: What is the material composition of the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set?\nA: stainless steel\nExample 3:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no", "answer": "There is not enough information to answer the question.", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE"}
{"id": "search_qa_27", "question": "Look, I don't have more than 10 bucks and I only trust Copper Chef and Ozeri. Find me a pan from one of those brands.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is a 10-inch pan appropriate for cooking meals for a single individual?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_62", "question": "What is the composition material of the USA Pan Hearth Bread Pan?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: What is the material composition of the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set?\nA: stainless steel\nExample 2:\nQ: What material is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of?\nA: stainless steel\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the USA Pan Hearth Bread Pan appropriate for baking gluten-free bread?\nA: yes", "answer": "aluminum", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B002UNMZPS"}
{"id": "search_qa_28", "question": "I'm looking for a pan, either copper or green, that can handle high temperatures. Which one can withstand the highest oven temperature?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "The provided product information does not include copper or green options that can handle high temperatures. However, the product information does mention that the Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12\", NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan can handle high temperatures up to 450 F.", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0"}
{"id": "fact_qa_63", "question": "Is the Cuisinart French Classic Pan dishwasher safe?", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE"}
{"id": "search_qa_29", "question": "I'm doing a lot of big batch cooking these days and I need a big pan that can handle high oven heat. What's the best pan you have that's at least 12 inches and can withstand the highest oven temperature?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS"}
{"id": "search_qa_30", "question": "I'm tired of those usual silver pans. Find me the biggest pan you have, just make sure it's not silver.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78"}
{"id": "search_qa_31", "question": "I'm only interested in Matfer Bourgeat or Ozeri brand pans. Can you find me the cheapest one from these brands?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00134LXEY"}
{"id": "fact_qa_64", "question": "Can the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set accommodate servings for two individuals?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for preparing meals that serve more than two people?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set suitable for cooking methods other than broiling?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU"}
{"id": "search_qa_32", "question": "I've been cooking with Norpro pans for years now, but they're just not heat resistant enough sometimes. Can you tell me what's their highest temperature-safe pan you carry?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set suitable for cooking methods other than broiling?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK"}
{"id": "search_qa_33", "question": "I'm tired of the usual black pans and I'm not a fan of Lodge's stuff. What's the first alternative you can offer?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_65", "question": "Does the Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet come already seasoned?", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_66", "question": "Is it necessary to cook with oil or butter when using the ZWILLING Spirit ceramic non-stick pan?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it necessary to grease a non-stick Madeleine pan prior to baking?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is seasoning required for ceramic non-stick pans before their initial use?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is greasing the pan necessary when using a pan with a high-quality non-stick coating for baking?\nA: no", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y"}
{"id": "search_qa_34", "question": "Look, I don't want to spend more than 30 dollars, and I need a pan that can handle heat above 600F. What's my cheapest option?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y"}
{"id": "fact_qa_67", "question": "Is the pan suitable for preparing meals that serve more than two people?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU"}
{"id": "fact_qa_68", "question": "Is this pot of appropriate size for preparing pasta dishes for a small to medium-sized family?", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964"}
{"id": "fact_qa_69", "question": "Is the T-fal fry pan dishwasher safe?", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78"}
{"id": "fact_qa_70", "question": "Is this fry pan compatible with an electric glass top stove?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0"}
{"id": "search_qa_35", "question": "I'm looking for a grey pan that can stand up to heat. Can you find me one that's above your average oven safe temperature, but keep it cheap?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78"}
{"id": "fact_qa_71", "question": "What is the country of origin for the final assembly of these pans with a GREBLON ceramic coating?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the GREBLON ceramic coating on cookware safe from releasing toxic chemicals when used at high temperatures?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set manufactured using authentic stainless steel?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Cuisinart saucepan manufactured in the United States?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_72", "question": "Does the Thermo-Spot heat indicator on the pan reliably indicate when the pan is sufficiently pre-heated?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the fry pan's stainless-steel handle remain cool when cooking on the stovetop?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this pan appropriate for stir-frying, which demands rapid and uniform heat distribution?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_17", "question": "Can this pan evenly cook my food, particularly during meat searing?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is this pan appropriate for evenly searing meat?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Will this pan allow my food to cook evenly on all types of stoves?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964"}
{"id": "fact_qa_73", "question": "Can the frying pan be safely cleaned in a dishwasher?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY"}
{"id": "search_qa_36", "question": "I'm looking for a pan that can withstand the heat of at least 450F and doesn't cost me more than 20 dollars. What's the largest one you have?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE"}
{"id": "search_qa_37", "question": "I'm sticking to a tight budget but still want quality. Give me the biggest pan you have from ZWILLING J.A. Henckels or USA Pan under $10.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00134LXEY"}
{"id": "search_qa_38", "question": "I ain't got more than 10 dollars. And my oven works like a blast furnace. So, could you find me an all-purpose pan that can withstand a temperature of over 600F and costs 10 bucks or less?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_74", "question": "Is the 1 1/2 quart saucepan large enough to accommodate larger canned items?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00008CM69"}
{"id": "fact_qa_75", "question": "Does the non-stick performance of the pan degrade after a month of use?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the pan become non-stick after proper seasoning and use over time?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: If I don't maintain this pan consistently, will its appearance alter over time?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM"}
{"id": "fact_qa_76", "question": "What is the volume capacity, in quarts, of this saucepan?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the 1 1/2 quart saucepan large enough to accommodate larger canned items?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the saucepan suitable for preparing delicate sauces and reductions?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this pot of appropriate size for preparing pasta dishes for a small to medium-sized family?\nA: yes", "answer": "2", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK"}
{"id": "fact_qa_77", "question": "Is the Cuisinart saucepan manufactured in the United States?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00008CM69"}
{"id": "fact_qa_78", "question": "Would the Madeleine Pan be suitable as a gift for someone who enjoys baking?", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00134LXEY"}
{"id": "fact_qa_79", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with the non-stick surface of this pan?", "answer": "No", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_18", "question": "Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?", "answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B00BK89AYS"}
{"id": "search_qa_39", "question": "I'm a fan of Presto and Chicago Metallic. Point me to the first pan you have from either of these brands.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set manufactured using authentic stainless steel?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B002UNMZPS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_80", "question": "Is the Copper Chef pan resistant to tarnishing and oxidation compared to traditional copper pans?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it safe to leave the Copper Chef pan on high heat for an extended period without causing damage?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the non-stick coating of this pan durable enough to withstand frequent cooking of acidic foods without damage?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Could the pan rust if it's not maintained correctly?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM"}
{"id": "search_qa_40", "question": "I always crank my oven up pretty high, like beyond 400F, and I want my pans in blue. Got anything that can handle all that?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Should oven temperature be reduced to avoid over-browning when using dark non-stick pans for baking?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_81", "question": "What is the duration of the warranty provided for the T-fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the T-fal pot contain any harmful toxins in its materials or non-stick coating?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pot considered lightweight by customers?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Cuisinart saucepan manufactured in the United States?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964"}
{"id": "fact_qa_82", "question": "Is the bottom of the frying pans designed to prevent oil from pooling at the sides?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it possible to cook in the Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan without using oil, and will the food not stick to the pan?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the ZWILLING Spirit Fry Pan prone to warping?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it necessary to season the All-Clad Stainless 10-inch fry pan in the same way as a cast iron pan?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0170TFNXM"}
{"id": "search_qa_41", "question": "I don't need any blue pans and I'm cooking for a large group, so it needs to be bigger than 8 inches. What's the first thing you'd recommend?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is a 10-inch pan appropriate for cooking meals for a single individual?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Are there particular considerations for what I should refrain from cooking in this pan?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00008CM69"}
{"id": "fact_qa_83", "question": "Is the Stone Earth Pan compatible with induction stoves for cooking?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this pan compatible with various stove types?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00BK89AYS"}
{"id": "search_qa_42", "question": "Cooking at high temperatures is my game. Get me the cheapest pan that can take the heat over 500F.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_19", "question": "I take pleasure in blackening fish; would this pan be suitable for such a cooking method?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I sometimes favor cooking with a grill. Would this pan be suitable for such a cooking technique?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this pan appropriate for evenly searing meat?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B00BK89AYS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_84", "question": "Is the cookware's handle designed to remain cool during cooking, and does it come with additional heat protection?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the fry pan's stainless-steel handle remain cool when cooking on the stovetop?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I use high heat while cooking with stainless steel cookware to avoid damaging the pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the saucepan suitable for high-temperature cooking on the stovetop without damaging its nonstick coating?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0"}
{"id": "search_qa_43", "question": "I'm a loyal fan of Chicago Metallic, but I ain't paying more than 20 dollars. What's the cheapest pan you got from them?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Stone Earth Pan lighter than traditional cast iron pans?\nA: yes", "answer": "ASIN not provided", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE"}
{"id": "search_qa_44", "question": "Listen, I'm picky about colors. You got any pans in either grey or blue? Just show me the first one that fits the criteria.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: What is the material composition of the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set?\nA: stainless steel", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_20", "question": "Is this pan appropriate for roasting a chicken?", "answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE"}
{"id": "search_qa_45", "question": "I have a strict requirement for oven-safe temperature to be at least 450°F and anything but green. What's the first pan you can recommend?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Are there particular considerations for what I should refrain from cooking in this pan?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_21", "question": "Is it safe to use my metal spatula with this pan without causing any damage?", "answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK"}
{"id": "search_qa_46", "question": "I ain't paying more than 10 dollars and I need a pan that's at least 12 inches. Can you find me a deal like that?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is a 10-inch pan appropriate for cooking meals for a single individual?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the 12-inch pan designed to accommodate the cooking needs of singles and smaller families?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE"}
{"id": "search_qa_47", "question": "I don't want to pay more than the average price and I really like copper color. Seriously, show me the first pan you’ve got that meets my criteria.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Stone Earth Pan lighter than traditional cast iron pans?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0"}
{"id": "search_qa_48", "question": "I do a lot of high temp cooking and only use Norpro gadgets. Do you have any pans that can take at least 500F? What's the ID of the product that can do this?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set suitable for cooking methods other than broiling?\nA: yes", "answer": "The product ID is not provided in the product information.", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0170TFNXM"}
{"id": "search_qa_49", "question": "I am not a fan of green and my cooking usually requires high heat. Which pan can withstand an oven temperature over 600F but isn't green?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964"}
{"id": "search_qa_50", "question": "I'm after a pan that's either grey or copper, and I'm not interested in breaking the bank. Can you find me the cheapest one you got?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Stone Earth Pan lighter than traditional cast iron pans?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS"}
{"id": "search_qa_51", "question": "I need a new pan, but I want it to be bigger than 12 inches and either green or blue. What's the cheapest one you got in those specifications?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the 12-inch pan designed to accommodate the cooking needs of singles and smaller families?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE"}
{"id": "search_qa_52", "question": "I ain't gonna throw over 30 dollars for a pan. Find me the biggest heckin' one in the budget.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y"}
{"id": "search_qa_53", "question": "I'm after a Matfer Bourgeat pan but don't have more than 50 bucks to drop. Get me the highest oven-safe one within my budget.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY"}
{"id": "search_qa_54", "question": "I plan on using my pan in the oven at pretty high temp, over 600 degrees, and I have a thing for copper or silver. What's the product that matches these preferences?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0170TFNXM"}
{"id": "fact_qa_85", "question": "Is the saucepan available for purchase within a cookware set offered by Anolon?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the T-fal A8572494 saucepan be used for cooking on high heat?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the saucepan suitable for preparing delicate sauces and reductions?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the saucepan suitable for high-temperature cooking on the stovetop without damaging its nonstick coating?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_22", "question": "Is this pan capable of retaining moisture while cooking vegetables to prevent them from becoming dry?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this pan suitable for recipes requiring prolonged high heat, like stir-frying?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the lid of this pan retain its non-toxic properties over time?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS"}
{"id": "search_qa_55", "question": "I need a reliable All-Clad pan that can withstand over 400F in the oven. What's the first one you've got that can take the heat?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "No", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964"}
{"id": "search_qa_56", "question": "I'm a big fan of \"Copper Chef\", and I'm looking for a pan that's bigger than average size. Also, I need it to handle high temperatures in the oven. Got anything like that?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is a 10-inch pan appropriate for cooking meals for a single individual?\nA: yes", "answer": "No", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_86", "question": "Is prior seasoning required for this non-stick ceramic coated pan before its initial use?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM"}
{"id": "search_qa_57", "question": "I'm a big fan of Bialetti, and I'm currently looking for the largest pan they've got. Which one is it?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Would the Bialetti pan be an appropriate gift for an individual who enjoys cooking and is willing to follow its care instructions?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan be used on induction cooktops or in the oven?\nA: no", "answer": "The product given is not a Bialetti pan.", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY"}
{"id": "fact_qa_87", "question": "Is it advisable to use cooking sprays on the nonstick surface of the pan?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78"}
{"id": "search_qa_58", "question": "I'm a big fan of Norpro, but I'm looking specifically for a pan that can stand a temperature above 450F in the oven. Can you find that for me?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set suitable for cooking methods other than broiling?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE"}
{"id": "search_qa_59", "question": "I like my pans to handle some heat in the oven, at least 400F, and they gotta be bigger than 8 inches. What's the most affordable one you got that meets these requirements?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE"}
{"id": "search_qa_60", "question": "Look, I'm after a really good pan but it's gotta be either blue or copper, just not Bialetti. Got anything that can handle the highest temperature?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan be used on induction cooktops or in the oven?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_23", "question": "Is this pan suitable for recipes requiring prolonged high heat, like stir-frying?", "answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_24", "question": "Do I require specialized cleaning agents for the pan to maintain its like-new appearance?", "answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_88", "question": "Does using cast iron cookware provide health benefits over nonstick pans due to its lack of synthetic coatings and iron contribution to food?", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_89", "question": "Does the pan's design include a raised center that could lead to uneven cooking?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Will this pan allow my food to cook evenly on all types of stoves?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the 12-inch pan designed to accommodate the cooking needs of singles and smaller families?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM"}
{"id": "search_qa_61", "question": "I'm not a fan of Ozeri at all. Which pan from any other brand can withstand the highest oven temperature?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "The All-Clad pan with the highest oven safe temperature is 600 F.", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS"}
{"id": "search_qa_62", "question": "I'm looking for a silver Presto pan, but I don't want to break the bank. What's the cheapest one you got?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y"}
{"id": "fact_qa_90", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with this pan without damaging its surface?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it safe to use metal utensils with the non-stick surface of this pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is it safe to use metal utensils with this pan, or is it better to refrain from doing so?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it safe to use metal utensils with this nonstick pan?\nA: no", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_91", "question": "Should I use high heat while cooking with stainless steel cookware to avoid damaging the pan?", "answer": "No", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_25", "question": "I like to blacken fish; will this pan suffice for such cooking?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I sometimes favor cooking with a grill. Would this pan be suitable for such a cooking technique?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?\nA: no", "answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78"}
{"id": "search_qa_63", "question": "I'm pretty particular about the brands I use in my kitchen. Get me the first product you have from either Anolon or All-Clad.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Does the product's nonstick coating contain PFOA?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y"}
{"id": "search_qa_64", "question": "I don't want to splurge but I'm a fan of All-Clad. Could you suggest a pan that doesn't cost more than 50 dollars from All-Clad?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE"}
{"id": "search_qa_65", "question": "I like to bake in high temperatures, and I need something sizable. What's the biggest pan you have that can withstand more than 600F in the oven?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0"}
{"id": "fact_qa_92", "question": "Is the pan designed for Madeleines suitable for baking other similar-sized desserts?", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00134LXEY"}
{"id": "search_qa_66", "question": "I'm only interested in Tramontina and All-Clad pans. Find me the cheapest one from these brands, will ya?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "answer": "There is no price comparison to be made.", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B002UNMZPS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_93", "question": "Is this saucepan dishwasher-safe?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK"}
{"id": "search_qa_67", "question": "I'm in the market for a new pan and I'm considering either All-Clad or Matfer Bourgeat, but only in either a copper or black color. Give me the first pan you find that matches those requirements.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this pan compatible with various stove types?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: What is the material composition of the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set?\nA: stainless steel", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY"}
{"id": "search_qa_68", "question": "I'm in need of a pan that can handle some serious heat, over 450F, and I only do black or silver in my kitchen. What's the best you got for me?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_94", "question": "Are the legs of this wok stand sturdy and durable for normal home use despite some users reporting issues over time?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this pan durable enough to handle frequent use for preparing various cuisines?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of durable material?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY"}
{"id": "fact_qa_95", "question": "Is it recommended to cook acidic foods in this pan before a good patina has been established?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY"}
{"id": "search_qa_69", "question": "I need a pan from the brand Chicago Metallic, but I don't wanna burn more than 10 dollars for this. Can you find any for me?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00BK89AYS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_96", "question": "Is the pan dishwasher safe?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY"}
{"id": "search_qa_70", "question": "I'm after a cheap pan that can handle some serious heat, at least 500 degrees. Find me something solid for under 30 dollars, will you?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is this pan appropriate for stir-frying, which demands rapid and uniform heat distribution?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this pan suitable for recipes requiring prolonged high heat, like stir-frying?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y"}
{"id": "fact_qa_97", "question": "Is the electric wok designed with rounded sides identical to traditional woks?", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY"}
{"id": "fact_qa_98", "question": "Is the heavy-gauge aluminum pan capable of distributing heat evenly?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does baking bread goods in a heavy pan affect the evenness of heat distribution?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this pan appropriate for stir-frying, which demands rapid and uniform heat distribution?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Will this pan allow my food to cook evenly on all types of stoves?\nA: no", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78"}
{"id": "fact_qa_99", "question": "Does the riveted silicone handle on this cookware maintain a cool temperature during use?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the fry pan's stainless-steel handle remain cool when cooking on the stovetop?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Do the riveted handles on kitchenware create challenges when cleaning around them?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the GREBLON ceramic coating on cookware safe from releasing toxic chemicals when used at high temperatures?\nA: no", "answer": "No", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78"}
{"id": "fact_qa_100", "question": "Does the pot feature a non-stick surface on both the interior and exterior?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Does the interior of the pot include measurement marks?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Does the pan's exterior offer the same durability and ease of cleaning as the interior?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964"}
{"id": "fact_qa_101", "question": "Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it safe to leave the Copper Chef pan on high heat for an extended period without causing damage?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the saucepan suitable for high-temperature cooking on the stovetop without damaging its nonstick coating?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Should I use high heat while cooking with stainless steel cookware to avoid damaging the pan?\nA: no", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0"}
{"id": "fact_qa_102", "question": "Is it recommended to store food in the refrigerator using these non-stick pans?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_103", "question": "Is it advisable to frequently cook acidic foods such as tomato sauce in this pan?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_26", "question": "Is it safe to use a metal spatula with this non-stick pan?", "answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE"}
{"id": "search_qa_71", "question": "I need a pan of at least 8 inches that can take more heat than your average pan. What's the first one you got that suits this?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is a 10-inch pan appropriate for cooking meals for a single individual?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this pan appropriate for stir-frying, which demands rapid and uniform heat distribution?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY"}
{"id": "search_qa_72", "question": "I can't spend tons on cookware, and I need a pan that withstands at least the average oven safe temperature, but costs under 20 dollars. Can you find one for me?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY"}
{"id": "search_qa_73", "question": "Listen, I only have 20 bucks to spend on a pan and I only trust Anolon or ZWILLING J.A. Henckels. So what's the best option you got for me?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_27", "question": "Is it safe to wash this pan in the dishwasher without concern for gradual damage?", "answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B0170TFNXM"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_28", "question": "Should I follow any particular precautions when cleaning this pan to preserve its surface?", "answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964"}
{"id": "fact_qa_104", "question": "Is there a lifetime warranty on the Cuisinart Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Cuisinart saucepan manufactured in the United States?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the saucepan dishwasher safe according to the manufacturer's recommendations?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00008CM69"}
{"id": "search_qa_74", "question": "I'm only interested in black or silver pans and I need it to withstand a pretty high oven temperature. Can you find me the baking pan that fits this criteria?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK"}
{"id": "search_qa_75", "question": "Look, I need a pan that won't break the bank, and it's gotta be bigger than your average size. Also, I need it to survive some serious oven time. Show me the one that ticks all these boxes.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY"}
{"id": "search_qa_76", "question": "I'm trying to save a few bucks here and I need a pan that can stand heat up to 400F. Can you fetch me the cheapest option you got?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_105", "question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set constructed using nonstick materials?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_29", "question": "I have quite limited cupboard space; is it possible to store this pan conveniently when it's not in use?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: My cupboard space is quite limited; is this pan designed for convenient storage when it's not in use?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is it recommended to store food in the refrigerator using these non-stick pans?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_106", "question": "Is cooking spray suitable for use with a Tramontina nonstick pan, or is cooking oil the better option?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it advisable to use cooking sprays on the nonstick surface of the pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is it safe to use non-stick spray on nonstick cookware without affecting its performance?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it necessary to grease a non-stick Madeleine pan prior to baking?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0"}
{"id": "fact_qa_107", "question": "Is greasing the pan necessary when using a pan with a high-quality non-stick coating for baking?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B002UNMZPS"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_30", "question": "I understand that certain pans require particular attention following use. Could you elaborate on the care needed for this specific pan?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: If I don't conscientiously maintain this pan, will its appearance alter as time goes by?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Are there particular considerations for what I should refrain from cooking in this pan?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Do I require specialized cleaning agents for the pan to maintain its like-new appearance?\nA: no", "answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE"}
{"id": "search_qa_77", "question": "I'm not made of money, I need a pan for my cluttered kitchen without breaking the bank. Can you show me the largest one you got for 20 dollars or less?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the 12-inch pan designed to accommodate the cooking needs of singles and smaller families?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is a 10-inch pan appropriate for cooking meals for a single individual?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE"}
{"id": "search_qa_78", "question": "I've got a beef with T-fal, so omit them. Show me the cheapest pan you got under 50 bucks.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this T-fal pan dishwasher safe?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no", "answer": "ASIN not provided", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0"}
{"id": "fact_qa_108", "question": "Does the stainless-steel cooking surface of this pan impart a metallic taste to food?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS"}
{"id": "search_qa_79", "question": "I'm no Rockefeller - I can't shell out more than 30 bucks. However, I need a pan that can stand up to high oven temperatures over 400F. Gimme the biggest one you got that fits that criteria.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE"}
{"id": "search_qa_80", "question": "I don't want any pans from USA Pan and it's gotta be bigger than 8 inches. Just show me one that fits the criteria, okay?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the 12-inch pan designed to accommodate the cooking needs of singles and smaller families?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is a 10-inch pan appropriate for cooking meals for a single individual?\nA: yes", "answer": "There isn't enough information in the provided data to give a specific ASIN number for a product that isn't from USA Pan and is bigger than 8 inches.", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B002UNMZPS"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_31", "question": "While simmering, I frequently face the challenge of adding water regularly to prevent burning. Can this pan assist in addressing that problem?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is this pan suitable for recipes requiring prolonged high heat, like stir-frying?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Are there particular considerations for what I should refrain from cooking in this pan?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I am in search of a multifunctional pan capable of both simmering soups and handling frying tasks. Would this be an appropriate choice for my needs?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_109", "question": "Does baking bread goods in a heavy pan affect the evenness of heat distribution?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B002UNMZPS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_110", "question": "Does the saucepan's nonstick coating contain the harmful chemical PFOA?", "answer": "No", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK"}
{"id": "fact_qa_111", "question": "Does this wok provide an effective traditional stir-fry cooking experience?", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY"}
{"id": "search_qa_81", "question": "I'm in need of a big pan that can take some serious heat in the oven. Pull up the first pan you got that's over 10 inches and can handle temperatures above 400 F.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_32", "question": "Do I need to purchase any extra cleaning supplies when I buy this pan?", "answer": "No", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY"}
{"id": "fact_qa_112", "question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set compatible with the size of a standard toaster oven?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set constructed using nonstick materials?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set suitable for cooking methods other than broiling?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set manufactured using authentic stainless steel?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU"}
{"id": "fact_qa_113", "question": "Is the pan considered convenient for storage?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: My cupboard space is quite limited; is this pan designed for convenient storage when it's not in use?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is it recommended to store food in the refrigerator using these non-stick pans?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this pan durable enough to handle frequent use for preparing various cuisines?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00134LXEY"}
{"id": "fact_qa_114", "question": "Does the T-fal pot contain any harmful toxins in its materials or non-stick coating?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964"}
{"id": "search_qa_82", "question": "I'm looking for a grey or black pan that can withstand a high heat in the oven - up to 600F. Can you find one for me?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_115", "question": "Do customers consider the Spirit Fry Pan's weight to be easily manageable?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pot considered lightweight by customers?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the ZWILLING Spirit Fry Pan prone to warping?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the 12-inch pan designed to accommodate the cooking needs of singles and smaller families?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y"}
{"id": "search_qa_83", "question": "I don't have a ton of cash to splash and I'm not a fan of Tramontina. So, which is the largest pan you have under 50 dollars from a different brand?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no", "answer": "yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY"}
{"id": "search_qa_84", "question": "I'm fixed on brands like Copper Chef and Norpro and I would prefer a silver or copper colored pan. Which product do you have that matches these specifications?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: What is the material composition of the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set?\nA: stainless steel\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set suitable for cooking methods other than broiling?\nA: yes", "answer": "No", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_33", "question": "Is it simple to recycle this cookware when it needs replacing?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the frying pan be safely cleaned in a dishwasher?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan dishwasher safe?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan dishwasher safe?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B00BK89AYS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_116", "question": "Are these pans dishwasher safe?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE"}
{"id": "search_qa_85", "question": "I'm not dropping more than 50 bucks on a pan, got it? Now show me the Utopia Kitchen or Copper Chef one that can withstand the highest temperature.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes", "answer": "ASIN not provided", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0170TFNXM"}
{"id": "fact_qa_117", "question": "Can the Copper Chef pan be used on an induction cooktop?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan be used on induction cooktops or in the oven?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM"}
{"id": "search_qa_86", "question": "No offense, but I don't want any of those Matfer Bourgeat pans. Can you find me the largest pan you have from any other brand?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no", "answer": "ASIN is not provided in the information, therefore I can only provide the size and brand of the largest pan I found from any other brand.", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY"}
{"id": "search_qa_87", "question": "Look, I only got a tenner to spend and I'm looking for a pan in either copper or grey color. What options do I have?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Are there particular considerations for what I should refrain from cooking in this pan?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_118", "question": "Is it possible for the wok to reach the necessary temperatures to sear meats effectively?", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY"}
{"id": "fact_qa_119", "question": "Is it necessary to grease a non-stick Madeleine pan prior to baking?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00134LXEY"}
{"id": "search_qa_88", "question": "I'm a bit of an amateur chef and I only trust USA Pan and Lodge pans. Which one of their products can stand the highest oven temperature?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "Neither", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00134LXEY"}
{"id": "fact_qa_120", "question": "Can the Stone Earth Pan safely be used in an oven?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this saucepan oven-safe?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00BK89AYS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_121", "question": "How does the nonstick performance of All-Clad pans compare to that of other brands in terms of food release and ease of cleaning?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the pan's exterior offer the same durability and ease of cleaning as the interior?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Does using cast iron cookware provide health benefits over nonstick pans due to its lack of synthetic coatings and iron contribution to food?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it safe to use non-stick spray on nonstick cookware without affecting its performance?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0170TFNXM"}
{"id": "fact_qa_122", "question": "Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0"}
{"id": "fact_qa_123", "question": "How user-friendly is the maintenance of the mirror polish on the pan?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Do I require specialized cleaning agents for the pan to maintain its like-new appearance?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I follow any particular precautions when cleaning this pan to preserve its surface?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: If I don't conscientiously maintain this pan, will its appearance alter as time goes by?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_124", "question": "Can these pans be used on an induction cooktop without issues?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan be used on induction cooktops or in the oven?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0170TFNXM"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_34", "question": "Is this pan designed to be presentable for table service?", "answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B002UNMZPS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_125", "question": "Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78"}
{"id": "search_qa_89", "question": "I ain't got tons of cash to splash and I need my pan to handle a hot oven. Show me the cheapest pan you got that can take 400F and still costs less than 10 dollars.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this pan appropriate for stir-frying, which demands rapid and uniform heat distribution?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK"}
{"id": "fact_qa_126", "question": "Is the saucepan designed for easy hand cleaning?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the saucepan suitable for preparing delicate sauces and reductions?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this saucepan dishwasher-safe?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the saucepan dishwasher safe according to the manufacturer's recommendations?\nA: no", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964"}
{"id": "search_qa_90", "question": "I'm not about to ruin a good pan in a hot oven and my wallet can't take a hit over 30 dollars. Show me your cheapest heat-resistant pan, safe for at least 500 degrees.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE"}
{"id": "search_qa_91", "question": "I need a sturdy pan that can take the heat above 400F and comes in either silver or blue. What's the largest one you've got in stock?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00134LXEY"}
{"id": "search_qa_92", "question": "I'm whipping up dishes that require some serious heat, above 450F. What's the largest pan you got that can handle that?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964"}
{"id": "search_qa_93", "question": "I got a big family to feed, need a pan at least 8 inches. Can you find me one that can handle the highest oven temperature?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU"}
{"id": "fact_qa_127", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils on this fry pan's nonstick interior?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it safe to use metal utensils with this nonstick pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is it safe to use metal utensils with the non-stick surface of this pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it safe to use metal utensils with this non-stick saucepan?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78"}
{"id": "search_qa_94", "question": "I need a pan that's at least 12 inches, but I didn't have a good experience with Tramontina. Show me the one with the highest oven-safe temperature you got.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan be used on induction cooktops or in the oven?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0"}
{"id": "search_qa_95", "question": "I'm cooking for a lot of guests. I need a big pan, atleast 12 inches. Also, the color should be either blue or copper. Can you help me find one?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the 12-inch pan designed to accommodate the cooking needs of singles and smaller families?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is a 10-inch pan appropriate for cooking meals for a single individual?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY"}
{"id": "fact_qa_128", "question": "Is the Bialetti 6168 Fry Pan compatible with a ceramic glass stovetop without causing scratches?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is this fry pan compatible with an electric glass top stove?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this pan compatible with various stove types?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE"}
{"id": "search_qa_96", "question": "I ain't looking to spend a fortune, but I need a pan that can withstand a 600F oven and doesn't cost more than 20 dollars. What's the biggest one you got that fits the bill?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE"}
{"id": "search_qa_97", "question": "I want a blue pan but nothing from Matfer Bourgeat. Gimme what you got.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: What is the material composition of the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set?\nA: stainless steel\nExample 2:\nQ: What material is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of?\nA: stainless steel\nExample 3:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes", "answer": "ASIN not provided", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_129", "question": "Does the Presto 5900 Electric Wok perform comparably to a gas burner for stir-frying?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does this wok provide an effective traditional stir-fry cooking experience?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the Presto 5900 wok be recommended for professional or commercial kitchen environments?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this pan appropriate for stir-frying, which demands rapid and uniform heat distribution?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_35", "question": "Are there particular considerations for what I should refrain from cooking in this pan?", "answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY"}
{"id": "search_qa_98", "question": "I'm looking for a high-quality pan. It needs to be oven safe up to at least 400F and bigger than 12 inches. What's the best option you've got?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY"}
{"id": "fact_qa_130", "question": "Are the non-stick ceramic coated pans dishwasher safe?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE"}
{"id": "search_qa_99", "question": "I'm looking to do some high heat cooking, so I need a pan that can take at least 500F. And no green ones, please. What's the best you got?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this pan appropriate for stir-frying, which demands rapid and uniform heat distribution?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU"}
{"id": "search_qa_100", "question": "Look, I'm a fan of Lodge and frequently cook at high temperatures. Show me a pan from Lodge that can withstand more than 600F in the oven.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_131", "question": "Is the T-fal Specialty Nonstick pot available for purchase as a standalone item rather than as a component of a larger set?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set constructed using nonstick materials?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Does the T-fal pot contain any harmful toxins in its materials or non-stick coating?\nA: no", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964"}
{"id": "search_qa_101", "question": "I'm looking for the largest pan either from Utopia Kitchen or Lodge, but nothing copper. Brass tacks - what's my best option?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Utopia Kitchen Cast Iron Skillet suitable for cooking a steak to medium-rare doneness?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM"}
{"id": "fact_qa_132", "question": "How does the quality of the USA Pan compare to pans from high-end baking stores?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the USA Pan Hearth Bread Pan appropriate for baking gluten-free bread?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B002UNMZPS"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_36", "question": "Will the coating of this pan deteriorate if it's subjected to regular dishwashing cycles?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can this pan withstand frequent washing if I regularly run my kitchenware through the dishwasher?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is it safe to wash this pan in the dishwasher without concern for gradual damage?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan dishwasher safe?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964"}
{"id": "fact_qa_133", "question": "Does this pan have a safe non-stick coating that prevents chemical exposure?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the saucepan's nonstick coating contain the harmful chemical PFOA?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the lid of this pan retain its non-toxic properties over time?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the non-stick coating of this pan durable enough to withstand frequent cooking of acidic foods without damage?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964"}
{"id": "fact_qa_134", "question": "What is the shape of the base of the wok, and is it appropriate for use on an electric heating element?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the electric wok designed with rounded sides identical to traditional woks?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Does this wok provide an effective traditional stir-fry cooking experience?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is sticking a common issue with this wok when cooking food?\nA: no", "answer": "Round, yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_37", "question": "Is this pan appropriate for dishes requiring frequent temperature adjustments?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is this pan appropriate for stir-frying, which demands rapid and uniform heat distribution?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this pan suitable for recipes requiring prolonged high heat, like stir-frying?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_135", "question": "Is the All-Clad E785S264 frying pan set compatible with induction cooktops?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0170TFNXM"}
{"id": "fact_qa_136", "question": "Is it safe to use the Anolon saucepan on high heat settings?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the T-fal A8572494 saucepan be used for cooking on high heat?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the saucepan suitable for high-temperature cooking on the stovetop without damaging its nonstick coating?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this saucepan oven-safe?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK"}
{"id": "search_qa_102", "question": "I don't need any small pans. Give me a big one, at least 8 inches, and it better be a USA Pan or Cuisinart. What's the first product you find?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is a 10-inch pan appropriate for cooking meals for a single individual?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the 12-inch pan designed to accommodate the cooking needs of singles and smaller families?\nA: yes", "answer": "ASIN not found", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0170TFNXM"}
{"id": "search_qa_103", "question": "I've got a pretty picky kitchen color scheme here, and I need a blue pan that can handle at least 400F in the oven. Got anything like that in your store?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y"}
{"id": "fact_qa_137", "question": "Is the pan's design conducive to balanced weight distribution for easy tossing and flipping?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for preparing meals that serve more than two people?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Will this pan allow my food to cook evenly on all types of stoves?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the 12-inch pan designed to accommodate the cooking needs of singles and smaller families?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE"}
{"id": "search_qa_104", "question": "I'm doing some heavy cooking and need an All-Clad pan that can handle more than 500°F. Which one would you suggest?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK"}
{"id": "search_qa_105", "question": "I do a lot of heavy-duty cooking and need a pan that's at least 10 inches and can stand a temperature of over 500F. What's the best one you have got?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU"}
{"id": "search_qa_106", "question": "No more than 50 bucks and I want something bigger than 8 inches. Find me the pan that can take the most heat.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is a 10-inch pan appropriate for cooking meals for a single individual?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this pan appropriate for stir-frying, which demands rapid and uniform heat distribution?\nA: yes", "answer": "ASIN not found", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM"}
{"id": "search_qa_107", "question": "I'm specifically looking for a bigger pan, over 8 inches, from ZWILLING J.A Henckels. Give me the cheapest option you have.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the 12-inch pan designed to accommodate the cooking needs of singles and smaller families?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY"}
{"id": "fact_qa_138", "question": "Are the cookware handles resistant to high temperatures during stovetop use?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the saucepan suitable for high-temperature cooking on the stovetop without damaging its nonstick coating?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Does the fry pan's stainless-steel handle remain cool when cooking on the stovetop?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Should I use high heat while cooking with stainless steel cookware to avoid damaging the pan?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE"}
{"id": "search_qa_108", "question": "I'm in need of a pan that's at least 12 inches, but not a fan of the color blue. Gimme the first option you have that matches my criteria.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the 12-inch pan designed to accommodate the cooking needs of singles and smaller families?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "answer": "yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU"}
{"id": "fact_qa_139", "question": "Does the pan's non-stick surface work as advertised?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the pan become non-stick after proper seasoning and use over time?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it advisable to use cooking sprays on the nonstick surface of the pan?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_140", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with this nonstick pan?", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_141", "question": "Is the GREBLON ceramic coating on cookware safe from releasing toxic chemicals when used at high temperatures?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_38", "question": "Is it acceptable to use a steel wool scrubber to eliminate persistent food remnants from this pan?", "answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B00BK89AYS"}
{"id": "search_qa_109", "question": "I'm looking for a pan that's either black or grey and from either Utopia Kitchen or Chicago Metallic. Just show me one.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no", "answer": "ASIN: B000000000", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0170TFNXM"}
{"id": "fact_qa_142", "question": "Is the French Classic Tri-Ply product line manufactured in France?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Cuisinart saucepan manufactured in the United States?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set manufactured using authentic stainless steel?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Cuisinart French Classic Pan dishwasher safe?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_143", "question": "Is it safe to cook with high heat using this nonstick pan?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is this pan suitable for recipes requiring prolonged high heat, like stir-frying?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the saucepan suitable for high-temperature cooking on the stovetop without damaging its nonstick coating?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0"}
{"id": "fact_qa_144", "question": "Are T-fal Professional fry pans compatible with metal utensils without losing their nonstick properties?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it safe to use metal utensils with this nonstick pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is it safe to use metal utensils with the non-stick surface of this pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it safe to use metal utensils with this non-stick saucepan?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78"}
{"id": "search_qa_110", "question": "I'm a Presto fan, but I'm not made of money. What's the cheapest pan you've got from them?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: What material is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of?\nA: stainless steel", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_39", "question": "Is it safe to routinely wash this pan in my dishwasher without causing any harm to it?", "answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0"}
{"id": "search_qa_111", "question": "Look, I've got 30 dollars to drop on a pan. I want a decent size though, no mini pans or anything. Find me the cheapest pan that's at least the average size out there.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00BK89AYS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_145", "question": "Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78"}
{"id": "search_qa_112", "question": "I don't want to drop more than 50 dollars and I'm only interested in Anolon. What's the cheapest pan you got from them?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no", "answer": "The product information provided is not from Anolon, it is from Ozeri, so it does not match the request.", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE"}
{"id": "search_qa_113", "question": "I'm over the basic black, and I need a pan that's larger than 12 inches. What's the first colorful one you can find for me?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the 12-inch pan designed to accommodate the cooking needs of singles and smaller families?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "answer": "yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00008CM69"}
{"id": "search_qa_114", "question": "I'm not the biggest fan of silver pans. Can you find me a pan that's either from Cuisinart or Anolon but absolutely not silver?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Does the stainless-steel cooking surface of this pan impart a metallic taste to food?\nA: no", "answer": "ASIN is not available in the given data.", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78"}
{"id": "fact_qa_146", "question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set manufactured using authentic stainless steel?", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU"}
{"id": "fact_qa_147", "question": "Is it advisable to wash these nonstick pans in a dishwasher?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Are these pans dishwasher safe?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Are the non-stick ceramic coated pans dishwasher safe?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan dishwasher safe?\nA: no", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0170TFNXM"}
{"id": "search_qa_115", "question": "I often crank up my oven to 400 degrees, and I only trust Utopia Kitchen and Ozeri. What's the first pan that can handle that heat from these brands?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this pan compatible with various stove types?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM"}
{"id": "search_qa_116", "question": "I've had enough of Presto, no more of their pans. I need a pan that can take the heat up to 500F in the oven. What's the cheapest option you got that isn't Presto?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_40", "question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is this pan durable enough to handle frequent use for preparing various cuisines?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for both baking and broiling?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B00134LXEY"}
{"id": "fact_qa_148", "question": "Does the pan's handle come with a loop designed for hanging storage?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: My cupboard space is quite limited; is this pan designed for convenient storage when it's not in use?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Does the fry pan's stainless-steel handle remain cool when cooking on the stovetop?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y"}
{"id": "search_qa_117", "question": "I ain't looking to break the bank here. What's the cheapest pan you have that's priced 20 dollars or less?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no", "answer": "yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B002UNMZPS"}
{"id": "search_qa_118", "question": "Look, I'm after a bargain. Find me a pan from either Cuisinart or Norpro that's less than 10 bucks, you got anything like that?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00BK89AYS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_149", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with this cast iron skillet?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it safe to use metal utensils with this nonstick pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is it safe to use metal utensils with this pan, or is it better to refrain from doing so?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it safe to use metal utensils with the non-stick surface of this pan?\nA: no", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS"}
{"id": "search_qa_119", "question": "I don't want any of those Matfer Bourgeat's stuff. Listen, I need a pan that can handle at least 600 degrees in the oven. Find me the biggest one for that.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964"}
{"id": "search_qa_120", "question": "Listen, I'm not one to splurge and I need a pan under 20 bucks that can handle above average oven temperatures. What's your best shot?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE"}
{"id": "search_qa_121", "question": "I'm trying to save some cash and need a pan that won't cost more than 20 bucks. It's got to be tough enough to handle oven temps above 400F. What’s the most affordable one you got that can do that?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0170TFNXM"}
{"id": "fact_qa_150", "question": "Does this pan provide even heat distribution during cooking?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is this pan suitable for recipes requiring prolonged high heat, like stir-frying?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this pan appropriate for stir-frying, which demands rapid and uniform heat distribution?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00BK89AYS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_151", "question": "Does the non-stick functionality of the pan remain effective over time with proper care according to customer feedback?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the pan become non-stick after proper seasoning and use over time?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: If I don't conscientiously maintain this pan, will its appearance alter as time goes by?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78"}
{"id": "search_qa_122", "question": "I'm looking to switch things up; no more Utopia Kitchen pans for me. Point me to the cheapest pan from a different brand, will ya?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE"}
{"id": "search_qa_123", "question": "I'm looking for a big pan, preferably larger than 8 inches. But hey, it's got to be in either blue or green. What's the first one you got?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78"}
{"id": "fact_qa_152", "question": "How durable is the non-stick coating on the T-fal saucepan according to customer feedback?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the saucepan suitable for high-temperature cooking on the stovetop without damaging its nonstick coating?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the non-stick coating of this pan durable enough to withstand frequent cooking of acidic foods without damage?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964"}
{"id": "fact_qa_153", "question": "Is it safe to use non-stick spray on nonstick cookware without affecting its performance?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78"}
{"id": "fact_qa_154", "question": "How durable is the All-Clad nonstick coating when used with proper utensils and care?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it safe to use metal utensils with this nonstick pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the non-stick coating of this pan durable enough to withstand frequent cooking of acidic foods without damage?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it safe to use metal utensils with the non-stick surface of this pan?\nA: no", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0170TFNXM"}
{"id": "fact_qa_155", "question": "Can the bread pan accommodate the baking of larger loaves for family gatherings?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the 12-inch pan designed to accommodate the cooking needs of singles and smaller families?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for preparing meals that serve more than two people?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan designed for Madeleines suitable for baking other similar-sized desserts?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B002UNMZPS"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_41", "question": "Is the lid of this pan designed to be easily handled by someone with arthritis?", "answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS"}
{"id": "search_qa_124", "question": "I love to cook with pans in the oven and often crank it up to 500F. Plus, I need a pan that's larger than 8 inches. What's the cheapest one you got that can handle all that?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78"}
{"id": "search_qa_125", "question": "I'm after a blue pan, just not from Anolon. Got anything like that in stock?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Would the Bialetti pan be an appropriate gift for an individual who enjoys cooking and is willing to follow its care instructions?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Do I require specialized cleaning agents for the pan to maintain its like-new appearance?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_156", "question": "Is seasoning required for ceramic non-stick pans before their initial use?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_157", "question": "Can the heating element of the wok be detached for cleaning purposes?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it possible for the wok to reach the necessary temperatures to sear meats effectively?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is sticking a common issue with this wok when cooking food?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the frying pan be safely cleaned in a dishwasher?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY"}
{"id": "fact_qa_158", "question": "Would the Bialetti pan be an appropriate gift for an individual who enjoys cooking and is willing to follow its care instructions?", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_159", "question": "Is there a warranty provided with the Stone Earth Pan?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Stone Earth Pan lighter than traditional cast iron pans?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the lid of this pan retain its non-toxic properties over time?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00BK89AYS"}
{"id": "search_qa_126", "question": "Listen, I don't want to dish out a lot of dough on a pan. Just find me a cheap one but it's gotta be safe in the oven up to at least 400 degrees, alright?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this saucepan oven-safe?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00134LXEY"}
{"id": "search_qa_127", "question": "I'm in need of a larger pan, nothing less than 8 inches will do. Go dig up the cheapest one you can find that measures up!\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the 12-inch pan designed to accommodate the cooking needs of singles and smaller families?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is a 10-inch pan appropriate for cooking meals for a single individual?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes", "answer": "ASIN:B00005EB1A", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964"}
{"id": "fact_qa_160", "question": "Is the pan designed to be dishwasher safe?", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_42", "question": "Is this pan appropriate for roasting a chicken?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is this pan appropriate for roasting a chicken?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I sometimes favor cooking with a grill. Would this pan be suitable for such a cooking technique?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78"}
{"id": "fact_qa_161", "question": "What is the exact weight of the pan?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Stone Earth Pan lighter than traditional cast iron pans?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: What is the material composition of the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set?\nA: stainless steel\nExample 3:\nQ: What material is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of?\nA: stainless steel", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_162", "question": "Is the wok designed to enable cooking with lower quantities of oil?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does this wok provide an effective traditional stir-fry cooking experience?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is it possible for the wok to reach the necessary temperatures to sear meats effectively?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is sticking a common issue with this wok when cooking food?\nA: no", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY"}
{"id": "fact_qa_163", "question": "What is the highest temperature the T-fal Professional fry pan can tolerate when used in an oven?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes", "answer": "400", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78"}
{"id": "fact_qa_164", "question": "What are the dimensions of the Copper Chef pan and how is its size suitable for serving family meals?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the 12-inch pan designed to accommodate the cooking needs of singles and smaller families?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is a 10-inch pan appropriate for cooking meals for a single individual?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no", "answer": "9.5 inches, yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM"}
{"id": "search_qa_128", "question": "I'm only interested in T-fal and Presto brands, give me a pan from either of them.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00008CM69"}
{"id": "search_qa_129", "question": "I'm looking to match my kitchen decor and only want either a black or copper pan. Can you show me one of your products in those colors?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: What is the material composition of the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set?\nA: stainless steel", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_165", "question": "Is the pan's handle designed to remain cool when cooking on the stovetop?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the fry pan's stainless-steel handle remain cool when cooking on the stovetop?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the saucepan suitable for high-temperature cooking on the stovetop without damaging its nonstick coating?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it safe to leave the Copper Chef pan on high heat for an extended period without causing damage?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_43", "question": "Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?", "answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM"}
{"id": "search_qa_130", "question": "I don't have a lot to spend but I love 'USA Pan'. What's their cheapest pan under 10 dollars?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is a 10-inch pan appropriate for cooking meals for a single individual?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00BK89AYS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_166", "question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set suitable for cooking methods other than broiling?", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU"}
{"id": "fact_qa_167", "question": "Do the riveted handles on kitchenware create challenges when cleaning around them?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78"}
{"id": "fact_qa_168", "question": "Is the pan compatible with induction stovetops?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this pan compatible with various stove types?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_44", "question": "My cupboard space is quite limited; is this pan designed for convenient storage when it's not in use?", "answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B00008CM69"}
{"id": "fact_qa_169", "question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Does the pan's exterior offer the same durability and ease of cleaning as the interior?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this pan durable enough to handle frequent use for preparing various cuisines?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_170", "question": "Is seasoning the pan necessary before using it for the first time?", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY"}
{"id": "search_qa_131", "question": "Look, I want nothing to do with Norpro or any green pans. What's the first product that fits that criteria?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set suitable for cooking methods other than broiling?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: What is the material composition of the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set?\nA: stainless steel\nExample 3:\nQ: What material is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of?\nA: stainless steel", "answer": "ASIN not provided", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_171", "question": "Is the temperature on this electric wok adjustable, and are users satisfied with its performance across different heat settings?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it possible for the wok to reach the necessary temperatures to sear meats effectively?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this pan appropriate for stir-frying, which demands rapid and uniform heat distribution?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY"}
{"id": "search_qa_132", "question": "Look, I'm not breaking the bank here. I need a pan from either Ozeri or Copper Chef that's not gonna cost me more than 20 dollars. What you got?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0170TFNXM"}
{"id": "fact_qa_172", "question": "Is a cover included with the Cuisinart FCT23-24NS Crepe Pan?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_173", "question": "Does the pan ensure even heat distribution to prevent hot spots during cooking?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this pan suitable for recipes requiring prolonged high heat, like stir-frying?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00BK89AYS"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_45", "question": "I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?", "answer": "No", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_46", "question": "Is it possible to use this pan immediately on an induction cooktop without any prior preparation?", "answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_174", "question": "Does the control panel allow for precise temperature adjustments and user-friendly interaction?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the T-fal A8572494 saucepan be used for cooking on high heat?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY"}
{"id": "fact_qa_175", "question": "Is sticking a common issue with this wok when cooking food?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY"}
{"id": "fact_qa_176", "question": "Is it possible to handle the cast iron skillet comfortably with just one hand?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS"}
{"id": "search_qa_133", "question": "I'm a big fan of Utopia Kitchen and Bialetti. Find me the largest pan from these two brands, will ya?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan designed for Madeleines suitable for baking other similar-sized desserts?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78"}
{"id": "search_qa_134", "question": "Look, I'm not trying to empty my wallet on a pan, got a 50 dollar limit here. Hook me up with the largest one I can get for that price.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B002UNMZPS"}
{"id": "search_qa_135", "question": "I'm looking for a big pan, something over 10 inches. Oh, and it's gotta be grey or copper. What's the first product that comes to mind?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is a 10-inch pan appropriate for cooking meals for a single individual?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00008CM69"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_47", "question": "Is this pan appropriate for stir-frying, which demands rapid and uniform heat distribution?", "answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY"}
{"id": "fact_qa_177", "question": "Should oven temperature be reduced to avoid over-browning when using dark non-stick pans for baking?", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00134LXEY"}
{"id": "fact_qa_178", "question": "Is this pot suitable for outdoor camping use, and what precautions should be taken during its use?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is this saucepan oven-safe?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Are there particular considerations for what I should refrain from cooking in this pan?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this pot suitable for cooking rice with minimal steam release?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964"}
{"id": "fact_qa_179", "question": "Is the non-stick coating of this pan durable enough to withstand frequent cooking of acidic foods without damage?", "answer": "This information is not provided in the product information.", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78"}
{"id": "fact_qa_180", "question": "Can you prevent having to manually clean the tiny holes in the pan?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Do I require specialized cleaning agents for the pan to maintain its like-new appearance?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I follow any particular precautions when cleaning this pan to preserve its surface?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the frying pan be safely cleaned in a dishwasher?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU"}
{"id": "search_qa_136", "question": "I'm not looking to spend more than 30 dollars and I want a pan that's black or grey. What's the cheapest one you got that fits what I'm looking for?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no", "answer": "18.55", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU"}
{"id": "search_qa_137", "question": "I'm not interested in All-Clad at all, so do me a favor and list the biggest pan from other brands you have available.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Are there particular considerations for what I should refrain from cooking in this pan?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?\nA: yes", "answer": "ASIN not provided", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0"}
{"id": "fact_qa_181", "question": "Can the flat-bottomed pan be used on a ceramic stovetop without issues?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this pan compatible with various stove types?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan be used on induction cooktops or in the oven?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00008CM69"}
{"id": "search_qa_138", "question": "I'm looking to add a bit of flair to my kitchen, either with a green or silver pan. Which is the most affordable one you've got?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no", "answer": "The T-fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot is grey, not green or silver, and is priced at $18.", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964"}
{"id": "search_qa_139", "question": "I'm trying to find a reliable pan from either All-Clad or Lodge that can withstand oven temperatures above 450 degrees. Show me the cheapest one you got.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00134LXEY"}
{"id": "search_qa_140", "question": "I'm looking for a big black pan, like, the biggest one you got. Can you find that for me?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the 12-inch pan designed to accommodate the cooking needs of singles and smaller families?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00BK89AYS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_182", "question": "How durable is the non-stick coating on the Green Earth Pan Set with regular use?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the non-stick coating of this pan durable enough to withstand frequent cooking of acidic foods without damage?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of durable material?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE"}
{"id": "search_qa_141", "question": "I'm doing up my kitchen in a grey and blue theme so find me the largest pan you got in these colors.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes", "answer": "ASIN is not provided in the product information, so I will respond with the product details instead.\n\nThe largest pan in grey or blue color is the All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver with a size of 12.", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_183", "question": "Is the pot designed to be lightweight or does it have a heavier construction for stability?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pot considered lightweight by customers?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this pot suitable for cooking rice with minimal steam release?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this pot of appropriate size for preparing pasta dishes for a small to medium-sized family?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964"}
{"id": "search_qa_142", "question": "I'm not looking to splurge, just need a pan under 20 dollars. It's gotta be either copper or blue though, can you find me one?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is a cover included with the Cuisinart FCT23-24NS Crepe Pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B002UNMZPS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_184", "question": "Does the fry pan's stainless-steel handle remain cool when cooking on the stovetop?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_48", "question": "Can this pan be used to roast a chicken?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is this pan appropriate for roasting a chicken?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I sometimes favor cooking with a grill. Would this pan be suitable for such a cooking technique?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM"}
{"id": "fact_qa_185", "question": "Is this pot designed to be compatible with a small burner?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is this pan compatible with various stove types?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this fry pan compatible with an electric glass top stove?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964"}
{"id": "fact_qa_186", "question": "Does the handle of this cookware retain heat during use, making it hot to the touch?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the fry pan's stainless-steel handle remain cool when cooking on the stovetop?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I use high heat while cooking with stainless steel cookware to avoid damaging the pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY"}
{"id": "search_qa_143", "question": "I can't stand anything from Chicago Metallic and I don't have more than 20 dollars to spare. Can you find me the largest pan from any other brand within my budget?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_187", "question": "Does purchasing this saucepan on Amazon.com come with a discount coupon?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet come already seasoned?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Cuisinart saucepan manufactured in the United States?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Do I need to purchase any extra cleaning supplies when I buy this pan?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00008CM69"}
{"id": "search_qa_144", "question": "I'm torn between ZWILLING J.A. Henckels and All-Clad for my pan purchase. Tell me the cheapest one from these brands.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_49", "question": "Are there any health risks linked to the materials utilized in this pan?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the lid of this pan retain its non-toxic properties over time?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan's lid retain its non-toxic properties over time?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Are there particular considerations for what I should refrain from cooking in this pan?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU"}
{"id": "fact_qa_188", "question": "Is it necessary to season the cast iron skillet before its initial use?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it necessary to season the All-Clad Stainless 10-inch fry pan in the same way as a cast iron pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Does the Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet come already seasoned?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is seasoning the pan necessary before using it for the first time?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS"}
{"id": "search_qa_145", "question": "I ain't throwing money around and I need to be able to slam this thing in a 400F oven. What's the cheapest pan you got that can handle that?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_189", "question": "Can the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan be used on induction cooktops or in the oven?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE"}
{"id": "search_qa_146", "question": "I'm a fan of T-fal and I do a lot of high-heat cooking. Can you track down a pan from them that can withstand at least 600 degrees in the oven?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_50", "question": "Is this pan suitable for direct placement on charcoal during a barbecue?", "answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK"}
{"id": "fact_qa_190", "question": "Is the Utopia Kitchen cast iron skillet compatible with all types of stovetops?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is this pan compatible with various stove types?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Utopia Kitchen Cast Iron Skillet suitable for cooking a steak to medium-rare doneness?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS"}
{"id": "search_qa_147", "question": "I'm a big fan of ZWILLING J.A. Henckels products. Show me the biggest pan they make.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the ZWILLING Spirit Fry Pan prone to warping?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no", "answer": "Not available", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY"}
{"id": "fact_qa_191", "question": "Does food cook evenly in the pans from this cookware set?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Will this pan allow my food to cook evenly on all types of stoves?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0170TFNXM"}
{"id": "fact_qa_192", "question": "Is the Norpro broiler pan compatible with induction stovetops?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this pan compatible with various stove types?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU"}
{"id": "search_qa_148", "question": "I'm in the mood for some fancy French cookware, but only if it's gray. Give me the biggest pan you've got from Matfer Bourgeat.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: What is the material composition of the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set?\nA: stainless steel\nExample 3:\nQ: Would the Madeleine Pan be suitable as a gift for someone who enjoys baking?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78"}
{"id": "fact_qa_193", "question": "Is the Cuisinart French Classic Pan available for purchase within a cookware set?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Cuisinart French Classic Pan dishwasher safe?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is a cover included with the Cuisinart FCT23-24NS Crepe Pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this pan compatible with various stove types?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE"}
{"id": "search_qa_149", "question": "I'm a big fan of Copper Chef, but money isn't growing on trees. Find me their most affordable pan, will ya?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_194", "question": "Is it possible to fry an egg in this pan without it sticking?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it possible to cook in the Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan without using oil, and will the food not stick to the pan?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can this skillet be used for both frying and baking?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it advisable to use cooking sprays on the nonstick surface of the pan?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y"}
{"id": "search_qa_150", "question": "I need a pan that can handle a high heat, over 400 degrees, and I only want it in black or silver. Show me the biggest one you got.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "ASIN not given", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_195", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with this non-stick saucepan?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964"}
{"id": "fact_qa_196", "question": "Is the 12-inch pan designed to accommodate the cooking needs of singles and smaller families?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE"}
{"id": "search_qa_151", "question": "I do a lot of cooking, and I need a big pan that can handle some serious heat. Give me your biggest heat-resistant pan that's over 10 inches.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is a 10-inch pan appropriate for cooking meals for a single individual?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the All-Clad Stainless 41106 10-inch covered fry pan designed for high-heat cooking and suitable for searing meats?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_197", "question": "Is the Bialetti 12-inch pan oven-safe?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is this saucepan oven-safe?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan be used on induction cooktops or in the oven?\nA: no", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_198", "question": "Is it safe to clean this pan with metal scouring pads?", "answer": "No", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00BK89AYS"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_51", "question": "Will the finish on this pan deteriorate if it goes through frequent dishwashing cycles?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can this pan withstand frequent washing if I regularly run my kitchenware through the dishwasher?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: If I don't maintain this pan consistently, will its appearance alter over time?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it safe to wash this pan in the dishwasher without concern for gradual damage?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B00134LXEY"}
{"id": "fact_qa_199", "question": "Is there a warranty included with the purchase of this saucepan?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Cuisinart saucepan manufactured in the United States?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the saucepan dishwasher safe according to the manufacturer's recommendations?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this saucepan oven-safe?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK"}
{"id": "fact_qa_200", "question": "Is the saucepan suitable for high-temperature cooking on the stovetop without damaging its nonstick coating?", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK"}
{"id": "fact_qa_201", "question": "Is a 10-inch pan appropriate for cooking meals for a single individual?", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE"}
{"id": "search_qa_152", "question": "I want a decent sized pan but I'm steering clear of Utopia Kitchen's stuff. Give me your best pan that's over 10 inches.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is a 10-inch pan appropriate for cooking meals for a single individual?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "answer": "yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0"}
{"id": "search_qa_153", "question": "I ain't dropping more than 20 dollars, and I only trust All-Clad or USA Pan brands. Give me the pan that can take the highest oven heat within my budget and preferred brands.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B002UNMZPS"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_52", "question": "Can the pan's lid retain its non-toxic properties over time?", "answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK"}
{"id": "fact_qa_202", "question": "Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0"}
{"id": "search_qa_154", "question": "I'm hunting for a pan, either blue or copper colored, but it's got to be from Norpro or Tramontina. Give me one option that checks these boxes.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: What is the material composition of the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set?\nA: stainless steel\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set constructed using nonstick materials?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: What material is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of?\nA: stainless steel", "answer": "ASIN is not provided in the information given.", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM"}
{"id": "fact_qa_203", "question": "What is the maximum number of people you can prepare a meal for using this electric wok?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for preparing meals that serve more than two people?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the Presto 5900 wok be recommended for professional or commercial kitchen environments?\nA: no", "answer": "more than two people", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY"}
{"id": "fact_qa_204", "question": "Does the pot come with a lid that seals tightly during cooking?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the interior of the pot include measurement marks?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the lid of this pan retain its non-toxic properties over time?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964"}
{"id": "fact_qa_205", "question": "How much does the Lodge Skillet weigh, and does it require two hands to handle it safely?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it possible to handle the cast iron skillet comfortably with just one hand?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the lid of this pan designed to be easily handled by someone with arthritis?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Can this skillet be used for both frying and baking?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_206", "question": "What specific material is the included spatula with the wok made of?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: What material is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of?\nA: stainless steel\nExample 2:\nQ: Is a metal spatula suitable for use with this non-stick pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: What is the material composition of the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set?\nA: stainless steel", "answer": "The product information does not specify the material of the included spatula.", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY"}
{"id": "fact_qa_207", "question": "Is it necessary to use oil or butter to prevent food from sticking on this nonstick cookware?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it safe to use non-stick spray on nonstick cookware without affecting its performance?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is it necessary to grease a non-stick Madeleine pan prior to baking?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it advisable to use cooking sprays on the nonstick surface of the pan?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_208", "question": "Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_53", "question": "Might the pan's shape render it difficult to stow in a drawer alongside other kitchen tools?", "answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964"}
{"id": "search_qa_155", "question": "Look, I got a max of 50 dollars and I need a pan that can survive in an oven temperature of at least 400F. Now, can you show me the best match for that?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B002UNMZPS"}
{"id": "search_qa_156", "question": "I'm not a fan of ZWILLING J.A. Henckels and I don't want to dish out more than 50 dollars. What's the largest pan you have that matches my criteria?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the 12-inch pan designed to accommodate the cooking needs of singles and smaller families?\nA: yes", "answer": "9.5 inches", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM"}
{"id": "search_qa_157", "question": "I’m looking for a big pan, something larger than 10 inches. It has be a Bialetti though. See if you can find one for me.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is a 10-inch pan appropriate for cooking meals for a single individual?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the 12-inch pan designed to accommodate the cooking needs of singles and smaller families?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Would the Bialetti pan be an appropriate gift for an individual who enjoys cooking and is willing to follow its care instructions?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK"}
{"id": "search_qa_158", "question": "I cook a lot in the oven and I need a pan that can handle at least 500F. And by the way, I'm not planning on spending more than the average price. So what's my best option here?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "No", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_54", "question": "Can the lid of this pan retain its non-toxic properties over time?", "answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78"}
{"id": "search_qa_159", "question": "I ain't paying more than 10 bucks for a pan. Dig up the cheapest black or blue one you got.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is a 10-inch pan appropriate for cooking meals for a single individual?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964"}
{"id": "fact_qa_209", "question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00134LXEY"}
{"id": "search_qa_160", "question": "I'm eyeing both Anolon and Ozeri but my wallet's crying out for mercy - it can just stretch out to 20 bucks. Give me the cheapest pan from these brands.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes", "answer": "The product provided is from ZWILLING J.A. Henckels and costs $5.59.", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y"}
{"id": "search_qa_161", "question": "I want a pan that can take some real heat and looks fancy too. Got any in green or copper that can handle more than 450°F? Show me the best option.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "No", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964"}
{"id": "fact_qa_210", "question": "Is the USA Pan Hearth Bread Pan appropriate for baking gluten-free bread?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B002UNMZPS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_211", "question": "Is the pan effective for cooking with low-fat methods without causing food to stick?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is greasing the pan necessary when using a pan with a high-quality non-stick coating for baking?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is it necessary to grease a non-stick Madeleine pan prior to baking?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_212", "question": "Is the saucepan dishwasher safe according to the manufacturer's recommendations?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK"}
{"id": "fact_qa_213", "question": "Is the saucepan suitable for preparing delicate sauces and reductions?", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00008CM69"}
{"id": "search_qa_162", "question": "Look mate, I don't want anything from Chicago Metallic and I need the pan to handle at least 500 F. Show me the biggest pan you got that meets these needs.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0"}
{"id": "fact_qa_214", "question": "Do customers find that the finished Madeleines have well-defined shell shapes?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan designed for Madeleines suitable for baking other similar-sized desserts?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Would the Madeleine Pan be suitable as a gift for someone who enjoys baking?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Might the pan's shape render it difficult to stow in a drawer alongside other kitchen tools?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00134LXEY"}
{"id": "fact_qa_215", "question": "Is the pan dishwasher safe?", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_216", "question": "Is the pan considered to have a good weight and balance for handling and maneuverability?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for preparing meals that serve more than two people?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_55", "question": "Is this pan compatible with various stove types?", "answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE"}
{"id": "search_qa_163", "question": "I'm only interested in silver pans from either Copper Chef or Cuisinart. What's the first one you got in stock?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is a cover included with the Cuisinart FCT23-24NS Crepe Pan?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK"}
{"id": "fact_qa_217", "question": "Is the Stone Earth Pan lighter than traditional cast iron pans?", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00BK89AYS"}
{"id": "search_qa_164", "question": "I got a thing about Matfer Bourgeat, don't ask. What other pan brands do you have? Show me any one of them.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: What is the material composition of the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set?\nA: stainless steel\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "answer": "Copper Chef", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM"}
{"id": "search_qa_165", "question": "I'm after a grey pan that can resist temperatures above 500F. Which is the largest one you got in stock?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU"}
{"id": "fact_qa_218", "question": "Are the riveted silicone handles of the cookware designed to maintain a cool temperature during cooking for a secure grip?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Do the riveted handles on kitchenware create challenges when cleaning around them?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Does the fry pan's stainless-steel handle remain cool when cooking on the stovetop?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the GREBLON ceramic coating on cookware safe from releasing toxic chemicals when used at high temperatures?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78"}
{"id": "search_qa_166", "question": "Listen, I've got around 30 dollars to shell out for a pan. Find me the one that can survive the highest oven temperature for that price.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_219", "question": "Is the lid of the skillet designed to create a tight seal when placed on top?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the lid of this pan retain its non-toxic properties over time?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan's lid retain its non-toxic properties over time?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the lid of this pan designed to be easily handled by someone with arthritis?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE"}
{"id": "search_qa_167", "question": "I'm a big fan of Anolon and Matfer Bourgeat pans. Can you tell me which one of their products can withstand the highest oven temperatures?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "Neither of their products are described.", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y"}
{"id": "search_qa_168", "question": "I need a pan that can handle extreme heat, over 600°F, and don't show me anything from Cuisinart. What's the first thing you got?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this pan appropriate for stir-frying, which demands rapid and uniform heat distribution?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78"}
{"id": "search_qa_169", "question": "I'm after a big pan, in grey or silver should do fine. Can you pull up the biggest one in those colors for me?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_56", "question": "I'm in search of cookware that can aid in quicker meal preparation. Do pans featuring glass lids contribute to a faster cooking experience?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Does using cast iron cookware provide health benefits over nonstick pans due to its lack of synthetic coatings and iron contribution to food?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_57", "question": "I am in search of a multifunctional pan capable of both simmering soups and handling frying tasks. Would this be an appropriate choice for my needs?", "answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B002UNMZPS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_220", "question": "Can this skillet be used for both frying and baking?", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS"}
{"id": "search_qa_170", "question": "I'm a big fan of Copper Chef and USA Pan. Get me the cheapest pan from either of these brands, will ya?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this pan compatible with various stove types?\nA: no", "answer": "This question does not match the provided product information, as the product is from \"All-Clad\" and the question is asking for \"Copper Chef\" or \"USA Pan\".", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_221", "question": "Should the pan be expected to emit odors the first time it is used?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is seasoning the pan necessary before using it for the first time?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan's lid retain its non-toxic properties over time?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the lid of this pan retain its non-toxic properties over time?\nA: no", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_222", "question": "Does the heavy-gauge aluminum bottom construction of this pan provide even heating?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Does the stainless-steel cooking surface of this pan impart a metallic taste to food?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_223", "question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of durable material?", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU"}
{"id": "search_qa_171", "question": "I'm so over silver pans. Find me the cheapest one you've got that's any color but that.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Stone Earth Pan lighter than traditional cast iron pans?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU"}
{"id": "search_qa_172", "question": "I'm in the market for a new pan - either blue or black. What's the cheapest option you got in those colors?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Do I require specialized cleaning agents for the pan to maintain its like-new appearance?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY"}
{"id": "fact_qa_224", "question": "Does the 10 1/4\" Lodge cast iron skillet effectively reduce oil splatter when frying chicken?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it possible to cook in the Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan without using oil, and will the food not stick to the pan?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can this skillet be used for both frying and baking?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it necessary to season the All-Clad Stainless 10-inch fry pan in the same way as a cast iron pan?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_225", "question": "Can the Presto 5900 wok be recommended for professional or commercial kitchen environments?", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY"}
{"id": "fact_qa_226", "question": "Is this pot suitable for cooking rice with minimal steam release?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964"}
{"id": "fact_qa_227", "question": "Is the ZWILLING Spirit 8\" Thermolon Fry Pan compatible with an induction cooktop?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_58", "question": "Will this pan allow my food to cook evenly on all types of stoves?", "answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM"}
{"id": "search_qa_173", "question": "I've got this thing for blue, so I need a blue pan. But I ain't a millionaire, so show me your cheapest option.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00134LXEY"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_59", "question": "Could the pan rust if it's not maintained correctly?", "answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_60", "question": "If I don't conscientiously maintain this pan, will its appearance alter as time goes by?", "answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE"}
{"id": "search_qa_174", "question": "I'm not breaking the bank for a pan but I don't want to skimp on quality either. What's your cheapest pan that can handle more heat than the average?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this pan appropriate for stir-frying, which demands rapid and uniform heat distribution?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this pan suitable for recipes requiring prolonged high heat, like stir-frying?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00BK89AYS"}
{"id": "search_qa_175", "question": "I got enough grey kitchenware as it is, and I need something bigger than 8 inches. What's the first non-grey pan bigger than 8 inches you've got?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is a 10-inch pan appropriate for cooking meals for a single individual?\nA: yes", "answer": "ASIN of the product (not provided in the question).", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE"}
{"id": "search_qa_176", "question": "I'm into big pans and only trust brands like USA Pan and Matfer Bourgeat. Give me the biggest pan you've got from either of those brands.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0"}
{"id": "fact_qa_228", "question": "How can the saucepan be maintained to look like new after multiple uses?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: If I don't maintain this pan consistently, will its appearance alter over time?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the saucepan suitable for preparing delicate sauces and reductions?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: If I don't conscientiously maintain this pan, will its appearance alter as time goes by?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00008CM69"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_61", "question": "Is this pan capable of withstanding high-temperature cooking such as searing a steak?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the All-Clad Stainless 41106 10-inch covered fry pan designed for high-heat cooking and suitable for searing meats?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this pan suitable for recipes requiring prolonged high heat, like stir-frying?\nA: no", "answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B002UNMZPS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_229", "question": "Is the interior of this saucepan designed to be non-stick?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the saucepan suitable for high-temperature cooking on the stovetop without damaging its nonstick coating?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is it safe to use metal utensils with this non-stick saucepan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this saucepan oven-safe?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964"}
{"id": "fact_qa_230", "question": "Is the All-Clad Stainless 41106 10-inch covered fry pan designed for high-heat cooking and suitable for searing meats?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS"}
{"id": "fact_qa_231", "question": "Is it possible to cook in the Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan without using oil, and will the food not stick to the pan?", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM"}
{"id": "search_qa_177", "question": "I'm looking for a decent sized pan from either Anolon or Chicago Metallic that can handle some serious heat. What's the product with the highest oven safe temperature you've got in stock?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM"}
{"id": "search_qa_178", "question": "I'm not really a fan of silver cookware, give me a pan of any other color. What's your top pick?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no", "answer": "yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_232", "question": "Is a Lifetime Limited Warranty included with the purchase of the pot?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pot considered lightweight by customers?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Does the interior of the pot include measurement marks?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Does the T-fal pot contain any harmful toxins in its materials or non-stick coating?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_62", "question": "I sometimes favor cooking with a grill. Would this pan be suitable for such a cooking technique?", "answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B002UNMZPS"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_63", "question": "Is this pan appropriate for evenly searing meat?", "answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_233", "question": "Is the pot considered lightweight by customers?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964"}
{"id": "fact_qa_234", "question": "Is it safe to leave the Copper Chef pan on high heat for an extended period without causing damage?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM"}
{"id": "fact_qa_235", "question": "Does the pot come with a pouring spout and built-in strainer in the lid?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is there a pour spout on this model of skillet?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Does the interior of the pot include measurement marks?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964"}
{"id": "fact_qa_236", "question": "Is the saucepan compatible with glass cooktops without causing any damage?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the saucepan suitable for high-temperature cooking on the stovetop without damaging its nonstick coating?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this saucepan oven-safe?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK"}
{"id": "search_qa_179", "question": "I'm gonna be using this pan in a pretty damn hot oven - needs to withstand at least 450F. Dig out the cheapest one you've got from ZWILLING J.A. Henckels for me.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE"}
{"id": "search_qa_180", "question": "I don't have time to browse, just tell me the first pan you have from either Lodge or Matfer Bourgeat.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this pan compatible with various stove types?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: What is the material composition of the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set?\nA: stainless steel", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0170TFNXM"}
{"id": "search_qa_181", "question": "I'm all about saving money and adding a little style to my kitchen, so find me the largest copper or green pan you got for under 10 dollars.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is a 10-inch pan appropriate for cooking meals for a single individual?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM"}
{"id": "fact_qa_237", "question": "Can the crepe pan effectively sear meats, achieving caramelization?", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_238", "question": "Does the Green Earth Frying Pan set maintain its non-stick functionality as intended?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the pan become non-stick after proper seasoning and use over time?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set constructed using nonstick materials?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE"}
{"id": "search_qa_182", "question": "I ain't trying to spend above 50 dollars and I want a silver pan. What's the cheapest one you have that fits my requirements?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY"}
{"id": "search_qa_183", "question": "I need a decent sized pan from either Presto or Ozeri that can handle some heat, but don't show me the tiny ones. What's the one with the highest oven-safe temperature you have?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE"}
{"id": "search_qa_184", "question": "I'm doing some heavy cooking and need a large pan that can take heat over 500°F. Can you find me the one that fits this description?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y"}
{"id": "search_qa_185", "question": "I'm a fan of copper pans, but I've had lousy experiences with Norpro. Get me a different brand, would ya?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set suitable for cooking methods other than broiling?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set constructed using nonstick materials?\nA: no", "answer": "yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00134LXEY"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_64", "question": "Is this pan compatible with my induction cooktop?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0"}
{"id": "fact_qa_239", "question": "Does the non-stick quality of the pan remain effective over time with proper maintenance?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the pan become non-stick after proper seasoning and use over time?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: If I don't maintain this pan consistently, will its appearance alter over time?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00BK89AYS"}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_65", "question": "Can this pan retain its new look over time without requiring much effort from me?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: If I don't maintain this pan consistently, will its appearance alter over time?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: If I don't conscientiously maintain this pan, will its appearance alter as time goes by?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Does the pan become non-stick after proper seasoning and use over time?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM"}
{"id": "fact_qa_240", "question": "Does the pan's design result in a reduced usable surface area compared to the total pan size?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the pan's exterior offer the same durability and ease of cleaning as the interior?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: If I don't conscientiously maintain this pan, will its appearance alter as time goes by?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the 12-inch pan designed to accommodate the cooking needs of singles and smaller families?\nA: yes", "answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU"}
{"id": "fact_qa_241", "question": "Is the Copper Chef pan compatible with induction cooktops?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM"}
{"id": "fact_qa_242", "question": "Is there a pour spout on this model of skillet?", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE"}
{"id": "fact_qa_243", "question": "Is there a warranty included with the purchase of the Cuisinart crepe pan?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is a cover included with the Cuisinart FCT23-24NS Crepe Pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Cuisinart saucepan manufactured in the United States?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE"}
{"id": "search_qa_186", "question": "I don't have money to burn, but I trust Utopia Kitchen and Norpro when it comes to pans. Can you find me the cheapest one they offer?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0"}
{"id": "search_qa_187", "question": "I’ve got a thing for silver or blue pans from either Norpro or Utopia Kitchen. Do you have one in stock?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Do I need to purchase any extra cleaning supplies when I buy this pan?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Does the Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet come already seasoned?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU"}
{"id": "search_qa_188", "question": "The pans I use go in the oven a lot, and I need something that can handle at least 600F, just no grey ones, okay? And I'm not made of money so hit me with the cheapest option please.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Should oven temperature be reduced to avoid over-browning when using dark non-stick pans for baking?\nA: yes", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY"}
{"id": "search_qa_189", "question": "I'm looking for a green pan and I don't want to shell out more than 50 bucks for it. Show me the cheapest one you got.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no", "answer": "no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78"}
